有人吗
Hey! Hello!
没事的 好吗？
Everything's okay. Okay?
放下 快扔了
Put it down. Drop it right now.
我是史蒂文·爱德华兹医生
I'm Dr. Steven Edwards.
这是道恩·勒纳警官 你感觉怎么样？
This is Officer Dawn Lerner. How are you feeling?
我在哪里？
Where am I?
亚特兰大的格拉迪纪念医院
Grady Memorial Hospital in Atlanta.
我怎么到这里来的？
How did I get here?
我的警官在路边发现了你
My officers found you on the side of the road
被一群行尸围住了
surrounded by rotters.
你的手腕骨折了
Your wrist was fractured
头部受了轻伤
and you sustained a superficial head wound.
你能记得你的名字吗？
Can you remember your name?
贝丝
Beth.
跟我一起的那个男人 他也在这里吗？
The man I was with, is he here, too?
你当时是一个人
You were alone.
如果我们没有救你 你也会成为行尸
If we hadn't saved you, you'd be one of them right now.
所以你欠我们的
So you owe us.
《行尸走肉》
一周前 有些人出去找补给了
Couple of them out there were on a run about a week ago.
他们在卡车停靠站
They found two boxes of Bisquick
找到了两盒饼干粉和一盒梅尔·哈格德的磁带
and a Merle Haggard tape at a truck stop,
还在桥下发现了这位先生
and then this gentleman under a bridge.
心搏停止 极度脱水
Cardiac arrest and extreme dehydration.
我尽力了
I tried to do what I could.
等等 就这样吗？
Wait, that's it?
如果病人没有好转的迹象…
If patients don't show any signs of improvement...
道恩就会下命令
Well, Dawn calls it.
等等
Hold up.
快点 尸体要冷了
Come on, body's getting cold.
有多少人住在这里？
How many people live here?
刚够让我们运转下去
Just enough to keep us going.
有些人一开始就在这里 有些人作为病人来了
Some of us started here, some came as patients.
大家都有工作
Everyone has a job.
我们不能埋了他吗？
Can't we bury him?
不行 有必要时我们才出去
No, we only go out when we need to.
这可能不是最庄严的尸体处理系统
It may not be the most dignified disposal system,
但我们只能凑合了
but we work with what we have.
我们成功保卫了楼梯井
We've managed to secure and guard the stairwells,
但是一楼的窗户碎了
but the windows are blown out on the ground floor.
行尸们听到声音 就会进地下室
Rotters find their way into the basement when they hear a noise.
如果尸体足够温暖
And if the bodies are warm or warm enough,
它们会吃掉它
they clean up some of the mess.
利用一切可以用的资源
Use everything you can use.
而且这是最快下去的方法
Plus it's the fastest way down.
你气色越来越好了
You're looking better and better.
那时我们有了一些枪支的线索
We had a lead on some guns,
所以我和搭档去了很远的地方
so me and my partner were pretty far out.
那时候我们看见了你
That's when we saw you,
在路上爬着
wriggling in the road.
你不记得我了啊？
You don't remember me, huh?
我在跟一只行尸搏斗
I was fighting a walker.
然后一切都变黑了
And then everything went black.
我们出现时 有一只在盯着你的大腿
Yeah, one was eyeing your thighs when we showed up.
但我先赶到了
But I got there first.
干掉了那只行尸
Jacked that rotter up.
我是戈尔曼
I'm Gorman.
别人帮了你的忙时
When someone does you a favor,
表示感谢是一种礼节
it's a courtesy to show some appreciation.
除非你想让我写下你占用的一切资源
Unless you want me to write down everything you're taking.
一切都有所代价 对吧？
Everything costs something, right?
我们会找到琼
We'll find Joan.
在那之前 你要洗衣服
Until then, you've got laundry duty
而我想要我的警服…
and I want my uniform washed ...
分开清洗 并且熨平
separately and pressed.
我知道
I know.
聪明鬼
Smart-ass.
我以前感觉就像溺在研究的海洋里
I used to feel like I was drowning in research.
现在这海洋枯竭了
Now the oceans are dry
我只能在无聊中窒息
and I'm suffocating in boredom.
你很幸运
You're lucky.
如果你都安逸到无聊了
If you feel safe enough to be bored,
那你就很幸运
you're lucky.
这是小金伯朗的歌 喜欢吗？
That's Junior Kimbrough. Do you like it?
我都想不起上一次听唱片是什么时候了
I can't remember the last time I heard a record.
这是身为这里唯一的医生的少数好处之一
It's one of the few perks I get for being the only doctor here.
有那个好处 还有这盘东西？
That and whatever this is?
小白鼠
Guinea pig.
你吃的那份呢？
Where's your food?
拿的越多 欠的越多 对吗？
The more I take, the more I owe, right?
你吃过小白鼠吗？
Have you ever tried guinea pig?
我想也没有
I didn't think so.
你吃过就不会管这叫好处了
You wouldn't call it a perk.
坐吧
Sit down.
不用告诉道恩 来
Dawn doesn't have to know. Come on.
怎么样？
Well?
秘鲁人喜欢吃
It's good enough for Peru.
这是卡拉瓦乔的作品
It's a Caravaggio.
我在高级艺术博物馆外的街道上捡到的
I found it on the street outside the High.
像垃圾一样丢在那里
Like trash.
很美
It's beautiful.
但它现在没有容身之所了
It doesn't have a place anymore.
艺术的宗旨并非生存
Art isn't about survival.
而是超越
It's about transcendence.
超越动物本能
Being more than animals.
崛起立于高处
Rising above.
我们不能再那样了吗？
We can't do that anymore?
我不知道
I don't know.
我喜欢唱歌
I sing.
我现在还在唱
I still sing.
- 又有新的伤员 - 找到了他的钱包
- We got a new one. - Found his wallet.
他叫加文·崔维特
His name is Gavin Trevitt.
从一楼的公寓摔下来 试图逃开几只行尸
Fell from a first floor apartment trying to get away from some.
他失了很多血 生命迹象在衰竭
He's lost a lot of blood and his vitals are dropping.
我觉得他活不了了
I don't think he's gonna make it.
- 我们已经给他太多汽油了… - 交给我
- We've already given him gas... - I got this.
你说你想救人 那就救他
You said you wanted to save people, so save him.
我都不知道他的伤有多重
I don't even know the extent of his injuries.
看看 他已经不行了
Look, this one's a loser.
你说过你不想让我浪费资源
You said you didn't want me wasting resources.
今天我想让你试试
Well, today I want you to try.
好吧 给心电图和超声波插上电
Okay, plug the EKG and the ultrasound into that battery pack.
快 很好 很好
Go. Good. Good, good, good.
接在病人身上
Now attach it to the patient.
张力性气胸 要穿肺
Tension pneumothorax. Punctured lung.
贝丝 给我从那柜子里拿一个空心针
Beth, I need a large hollow needle in that cabinet.
能救活吗？
Is he gonna make it?
他从楼上摔了下来 道恩
He fell from a building, Dawn.
能救活吗
Is he going to make it?
看见这些淤青了吗？
You see these bruises?
是内出血
He has internal bleeding,
但我需要分层扫描才能知道有多严重
but I need a CAT scan to know how bad.
就算我知道了出血程度
And even if I could determine that,
我也没有能救他的工具
I don't have the tools to save him.
告诉你了 这是浪费资源
I told you, this was a waste of resources.
史蒂文 给我搞清楚局面
Steve, try to grasp the stakes here.
- 她总是这样吗 - 只有心情不好的时候
- Is she always like that? - Only on her bad days.
不幸的是 她心情永远不好
It's unfortunate for us that's the only kind she has.
诺亚给你留了件新衬衫
Noah left you a new shirt.
这件怎么了？
What's wrong with this one?
她爱干净
She likes things neat.
那她肯定喜欢你的办公室
She must love your office.
我们都以不同的方式为她效力
We all have ways of making her pay.
我在门外等你
I'll wait for you outside.
道恩叫你 快来
Dawn needs you, now.
幸好我们发现了她
She's lucky we found her.
不管你想做什么 都不值得
Whatever you were thinking, it wasn't worth it.
现在你有两个选择
Okay, you have two choices.
要么我们帮你截肢 要么你自己来
Either we cut off your arm or you do.
去你妈的 还有你的小婊子
Screw you and your little bitch!
- 自以为是的荡妇 - 戈尔曼 出去
- Smart-ass whore. - Gorman, get out of here!
这是麻醉剂 你用得着
It's anesthetic. You need it.
- 去死吧 - 她已经做出选择了 快动手
- Go to hell. - She made her choice. Do it.
动手
Do it.
不 不 放开我
No, no, no! I said leave me alone!
我们绝不会见死不救
We're not going to let you die.
不会眼睁睁地看你尸变
We are not going to let you turn.
你去哪儿？
Where do you think you're going?
- 我帮不上忙 - 你想让她死吗？
- I can't help. - Do you want her to die?
贝丝 帮我们压住她
Beth, I need you to hold her down.
快来 快
Do it now. Now.
- 没事的 没事的 - 快来
- It's okay. It's okay. - Come on.
别碰我
Keep your hands off me!
我才不会回他那儿去
I'm not going back to him!
你不用回去
You don't have to.
- 你控制不了他们 - 我会的
- You can't control them. - I will.
贝丝 准备好了吗？
Beth, you ready?
你没事吧？
You okay?
我是诺亚
I'm Noah.
"棒棒糖协会"的
Of the Lollipop Guild.
我叫贝丝
Beth.
多谢
Thanks for that.
我觉得上午的事过后 你可以吃点糖
Figured you could use a pick-me-up
换换心情
after this morning.
早知道我就把整罐糖都拿来了
Guess I should have brought the whole jar.
这件应该合身
Here, this should fit.
你知道琼是怎么回事吗？
You know what happened with Joan?
她留下来 工作了一段时间
If she'd have stayed, worked for a while,
她不能等康复了直接走吗？
couldn't she have just left?
至少我没见到过这种情况
I haven't seen it work like that yet.
你在这儿工作多久了
How long have you been here?
差不多有1年吧
I guess about a year.
我跟我老爸被人发现的时候 都是奄奄一息
Dad and I were both pretty messed up when they found us.
他们说只能救活一个
They said that they could only save one.
我一直被蒙在鼓里
For the longest time, I actually believed them.
如今才明白
Now I get it.
老爸要高大 强壮许多
Dad was bigger, stronger.
肯定会反抗
Would have fought back.
给他们造成威胁
Would have been a threat.
那他们是故意不救他的吗？
They left him behind on purpose?
道恩对这事睁一只眼闭一只眼
And Dawn just looked the other way.
看似她在掌控全局 实则不然
See, she's in charge, but just barely.
情况越来越糟
And it's getting worse.
所以一旦时机成熟 我就要离开这儿
It's why I'm out of here when the time is right.
去找我的叔叔
I came looking for my uncle.
然后再接老妈
Gotta get back to my mom.
你家在哪里？
Where's home?
里士满
Richmond.
弗吉尼亚的首府
Virginia.
我们那儿有高墙
We had walls.
他们看我骨瘦如柴
See, they think I'm scrawny.
以为我不堪一击
They think I'm weak.
但其实他们一点也不了解我
But they don't know shit about me.
不了解我是什么人
About what I am.
不了解你是什么人
About what you are.
夏普德 你已经连值两班了
Shepherd, you've already pulled a double.
现在换我吧
I got it from here.
是的 长官
Yes, ma'am.
谢了
Thanks.
我知道你还没吃早餐
I know you didn't have breakfast.
这是停战协议？
Peace treaty?
我不用吃很多的
I don't need much.
我不会受你逼迫留很久的
I'm not staying any longer than you make me.
你不应该把这看成坐牢
You know, you shouldn't see this as a sentence.
我给你提供食物 衣服 保护
I'm giving you food, clothes, protection.
这些东西从来都不是免费的
When have those things ever been free?
我从没主动向你求助
I never asked for your help.
但你确实需要我的帮助
But you needed it.
试着看看我们做的好事
Try to look at the good we're doing.
就算很艰难 我们还是救了琼一命
Hard as it was, we saved Joan's life.
救了崔维特一命 我们还救了你一命
Trevitt's life. We saved your life.
我维持着这里的运转
I'm keeping all of us going here.
这可不是件小事
That is not a small thing.
我们付出了很多才变成今天这样 贝丝
It's taken a lot to get us here, Beth.
而我相信灾变之前的生活
And I believe that what we had before all of this
并未终结
isn't over.
等我们最终得救了
And when we're finally rescued,
等噩梦结束了
when this nightmare ends,
我们会需要重建的
we're gonna need to rebuild.
你不会真的认为有人会来救我们吧？
You don't really think someone's coming for us?
还有像我们一样的人存在 贝丝
There's still people like us, Beth.
有试图维护世界 重建秩序的人
People trying to keep the world alive, to fix it.
在那之前 我们都得贡献一份力量
Until then, we all have to contribute.
都得妥协让步
To compromise.
有得到 就要有回报
If we take, we give back.
这样才公平
It's only fair.
所以继续回报你欠我们的
So keep working off what you owe
然后你很快就可以离开了
and you'll be out of here in no time.
- 假如你想离开的话 - 我想
- If that's what you want. - It is.
那你就得吃东西
Well, then you have to eat.
不然的话 你会变得虚弱
Otherwise, you'll get weak.
你不能好起来 你会需要更多的治疗
You won't heal, you'll require more treatment,
然后你就不能工作了
and you won't be able to do your job.
我知道你情非得已
I know you didn't ask for this.
我也是
I didn't either.
你唱得真好
That's really nice.
我去叫爱德华兹医生
I'll get Dr. Edwards.
不要 拜托
No, please.
先别叫
Not yet.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
她可以控制他们的
She can control them.
但她没有 因为这样更简单一些
But she doesn't because it's easier.
因为她是个懦夫
Because she's a coward.
他对你做了什么？
What did he do to you?
这不重要
It doesn't matter.
我猜当本人不用付出代价时
I guess it's easy to make a deal with the devil
就能轻易地和恶魔做交易了
when you're not the one paying the price.
有东西不见了吗？
Lose something?
这是你的吧？
This is yours, ain't it?
青苹果味的
Sour apple.
和道恩从儿科那里找来的一样
Like the kind Dawn acquired from pediatrics.
你可以尝一尝
Suppose you could have a taste.
看看能不能想起来这个味儿
See if it rings any bells.
我不想吃
I don't want it.
来吧
Oh, come on, now.
我只是想确认一下我把这糖还对人了
I just want to be sure I'm returning this to its rightful owner.
没错 这就对了
Yeah. That's right.
- 很好 很好 - 别烦她
- That's right. That's right. - Leave her alone.
这姑娘是我的
The girl should have been mine.
谁都不是你的 戈尔曼
Nobody's yours, Gorman.
谁都不是
Nobody.
如果你认为你能让琼回到…
And if you think you're getting Joan back...
我会让她回来的
Oh, I'm gonna get her back.
你认为道恩会阻止我吗？
You think Dawn's gonna stop me?
我会阻止你
I will.
你是在替人出头吗 医生？
You stepping up, Doc?
你生病的时候会怎么样呢 戈尔曼？
What happens when you get sick, Gorman?
你伤口什么时候感染的？
When you get an infection?
当你被咬时？
When you get bit?
我觉得会有医生治疗我
I think there's gonna be somebody,
除你之外的医生
somebody who ain't you.
戈尔曼
Gorman.
也许有人能顶替她掌管一切呢
And maybe somebody in charge who ain't her.
你为什么留在这？
Why do you stay?
你随时可以走的
You could leave whenever you want.
为什么要留在这里？
Why do you stay here?
欢迎来到格拉迪纪念医院的一层
Welcome to the ground floor of Grady Memorial Hospital.
这里不是出路
This isn't a way out.
没有出路
There isn't one.
从这里不行
Not from here.
为什么要带我来这？
Why'd you bring me here?
看着
Watch.
每当我开始想太多
When I start thinking about it too much,
我就下来看看这幅场景
I come down to look at this.
为什么要带我来这？
Why'd you bring me here?
因为你问我为什么要留下
You asked why I stay.
来吧
Come on.
我给你讲个故事
Let me tell you a story.
当灾变爆发的时候
When everything started,
道恩听命于一个叫汉森的人
Dawn reported to a guy named Hanson.
他们被派来清空医院
They had orders to clear the hospital
把大家转移到巴特勒公园去
and move everyone to Butler Park.
差不多在午夜时 我们听到飞机声
It was close to midnight when we heard the jets,
爆炸声
the bombs.
哭喊声
The screams.
我那时正在三楼
I was on the third floor.
道恩和汉森的小队正在进行最后的搜查
Dawn and Hanson's teams were doing a final sweep.
我们知道情况不妙
And we knew it was bad.
但是来这里后 我们才知道到底有多糟
Just didn't know how bad till we came up here.
城市沦陷了
The city had fallen.
我们疏散的所有人…
And everyone we evacuated...
他们都不在了
they were just gone.
起初我们几乎足不出户
We kept mostly to ourselves at first,
直到食物吃光了
till the food ran out.
我们开始每次派一些人出去搜寻补给
We started going out on runs, a few of us at a time.
我们会看到需要帮助的人们
We'd see people who needed help.
他们在苦苦支撑 但是…
Barely holding on. But ...
我们也自身难保
we were barely holding on ourselves.
后来 我实在无法视而不见了
Came a time I couldn't look away anymore.
我发现了一个孩子
I found this kid.
他的衣服被凝固汽油弹烧着了
Napalm burns on his clothes,
皮肤被烧伤了
his skin.
道恩说我们分不出资源
Dawn said we couldn't spare the resources.
所以我们达成了一个协议
So we struck a deal.
我尽力救他
I'd use what I could to heal him
而他必须通过劳动来回报我们
and he'd compensate us for those resources through service.
现在…
Now...
你不是问题所在
You're not the problem.
我们失去了很多人
We lost people.
这就是问题所在
That was the problem.
汉森崩溃了 他做了几个决定
Hanson cracked. He made some calls
害死了几个人
that got people killed.
道恩解决了问题
Dawn took care of things.
她干掉了他
She took care of him.
她带领我们经历艰险
She saw us past it.
把我们团结在一起
Kept us together.
保证每个人都活下去
Kept us alive.
你管这样的日子叫活着吗？
You call this living?
我们还在呼吸啊
We're still breathing.
我们带来的那些病人 他们也还在呼吸
Patients we brought here, they're still breathing.
如果在这些围墙外 孤立无援
Outside these walls, alone, unprotected,
他们和我们都活不下去
they'd be dead. We'd be dead.
我们俩在外面坚持不下去
We're not the ones who make it.
情况虽然很糟
As bad as it gets,
但这里至少比外面安全
it's still better than down there.
我该回去了
I should get back.
你顺便去看一下崔维特先生
How about you look in on Mr. Trevitt
然后今天就到此为止吧
and call it a day?
好的
Okay.
他病情稳定 还要注射75毫克氯氮平
He's stable, due for another 75mg of Clozapine.
明天我们从头来过
And tomorrow we'll start fresh.
好的
Sure.
还在忙吗？
Still at it, huh?
不
No.
怎么了？
What?
不要
No.
你们对他做了什么？
What did you do to him?
我…
I... I...
之前他很稳定 直到你俩与他独处一室
He was fine until the two of you were alone with him.
一定是发生了什么
Something happened.
你跟我实话实说
I want you to tell me.
这是个意外 贝丝出去拿纱布
It was an accident. Beth left to get some gauze.
我在擦地 可能不小心拔掉了呼吸机
I was mopping. I must have unplugged the ventilator somehow.
- 只停了一分钟而已 - 不是…
- It only stopped for a minute. - But that's...
然后我又插上了
I got it working again.
把他带去我办公室
Take him to my office.
道恩 这只是个意外
Dawn, it was an accident.
这只是个意外
It was an accident.
事实不是这样的
That's not what happened.
他突然开始抽搐
He just... he just started seizing.
抽搐？
Seizing?
你给他注射了氯硝安定 对吧？
Well, you gave him Clonazepam, right?
氯 氯氮平
Cloz... Clozapine.
你说的是氯氮平
You said Clozapine.
不 我不是那样说的
No, I didn't.
求你们了
Please!
贝丝 趁着崔维特先生的尸体还没冷
Beth, we need to deal with Mr. Trevitt
我们得把他处理掉
while he's still warm.
我必须阻止他们
I have to stop it!
求了 住手
Please, stop!
- 求了 - 我们阻止不了 你阻止不了
- Please! - We can't... you can't stop it.
你以为我不知道吗？
You really think I didn't know?
诺亚很聪明
Noah's smart.
也许是我最优秀的工人
Probably my best worker.
但是他说的呼吸机的事
But that story he told about the ventilator?
这孩子不太会说谎
Boy's not much of a liar.
如果你早就知道了 为什么你不…
If you knew, then why did you...
我也不想那样做 但我必须如此
I didn't want to. I had to.
一个好人的无心之过差点把一切都毁了
A good man's mistakes almost ended everything for us,
若让这样的事重演 那我就太该死了
and I'll be damned if I'm gonna let that happen again.
我们做出的牺牲都是为了大我的利益
Every sacrifice we make needs to be for the greater good.
一旦不是 一旦我们忽视了这点
The second it isn't, the second we lose sight of that,
一切就都完了
it's all over.
问题是 你并不属于大我
The thing is, you're not the greater good.
- 你不够强壮 - 我很强壮
- You're not strong enough. - I am strong.
多少人需要冒着生命危险来救你？
How many people had to risk their lives to save you?
在这里 你也是体制的一份子
In here, you are part of a system.
受保护者们能让我的警官开心
The wards keep my officers happy.
我的警官越是开心
The happier my officers are,
他们就越会努力地帮助我们继续下去
the harder they work to keep us going.
这并不容易
And this hasn't been easy.
大家都做出了妥协
There have been compromises,
但是确实管用
but it's working.
他们救了我们之后
And after they rescue us,
我们就能让世界重建秩序
we're gonna help put the world back together.
因为我们一直在坚持着
Because we're the ones holding on.
这就是我们在这里做的好事
That's the good we're doing here.
也是你要做的好事
That's the good you're doing here.
因为这才让你有所价值
That's what makes you worth something.
但在外面…
But out there...
你毫无价值
you are nothing.
要么死 要么成为别人的负担
Except dead or somebody's burden.
- 胡扯 - 是吗？
- That's bullshit. - Oh, yeah?
你来的那晚上我就看到了这个
I saw this the night you came in.
这也是胡扯吗？
Is this bullshit, too?
有的人注定不能接受这种生活 但没关系
Some people just aren't meant for this life, and that's okay.
只要他们不占那些能接受的人的便宜就好
As long as they don't take advantage of the ones who are.
没看上去那么糟啦
It's not as bad as it looks.
我没事
I'm okay.
你看
Watch.
有止痛药 基本不疼了
Painkillers. It barely even hurts.
道恩需要崔维特来帮忙
Dawn needed Trevitt for something.
我知道那就是原因所在
I know that's what that was about.
糟糕的是
Screwed-up thing is,
她也被困住了
she's trapped, too.
我们没被困住
We're not trapped.
我跟你一起走
I'm going with you.
从地下室出去最快
Basement's the fastest way out.
但凡有一点动静 都会招来行尸
Any noise and we got rotters.
那我们就无声无息的
So we won't make noise.
我可以盯着道恩
I can keep an eye on Dawn.
她办公室里有一把电梯组的备用钥匙
She keeps a spare key to the elevator banks somewhere in her office.
你能找到吗？
Think you can find it?
能
Yeah.
(去你妈的)
你好啊
Hey there.
希望没有打扰到你
I hope I'm not interrupting.
道恩要我拿她的钥匙
Dawn was just asking for her key.
是吗？
Was she, now?
我刚刚跟道恩在一起
See, I was just with Dawn
但我不记得她说过
and I don't seem to remember that.
没关系
It's okay.
也许不必让她知道
Maybe she doesn't have to know.
也许还有别的办法
Maybe there's another solution.
你懂吗？
You know?
让你我双赢的办法
A little win-win for both of us.
怎么样 贝丝？
So how about it, Bethy?
就在这里解决好吗？
We gonna work something out here?
好姑娘
Good girl.
琼 她就不太配合
Now, Joan, she's not such a team player.
我运气真不错
Lucky for me...
你就不怎么好斗
you're not a fighter.
可能只是电池的问题
Yeah, it may just be the battery.
我去找个新的来
I'll stop in and grab another one.
好
Okay.
贝丝
Beth.
一切还好吗？
Everything okay?
琼在找你
Oh, Joan was looking for you.
我看到她和戈尔曼朝你办公室去了
I saw her and Gorman headed towards your office.
谢谢 贝丝
Thank you, Beth.
准备好了吗？
Ready?
好了
Yeah.
你安全后 我爬下去
Once you're safe, I'll climb down.
好的
Okay.
诺亚？
Noah?
诺亚？诺亚？
Noah? Noah?
你能走路吗？
Can you walk?
- 能 我没事 - 好
- Yeah, I'm okay. - Okay.
那里
There.
救命
Help.
你他妈的以为自己是谁？
Who the hell do you think you are?
他攻击了我
He attacked me.
就像他攻击了琼一样
Just like he attacked Joan.
而你放任他不管
Just like you let him.
你知道这里发生了什么 却放任不管
You know what's happening here and you let it happen.
- 你任凭这一切发生 - 这是为了坚持下去
- You're letting it happen. - So that we make it.
没人会来救我们 道恩
No one's coming, Dawn.
没人会来
No one's coming.
我们都会死 而你白白任凭这一切发生
We're all gonna die and you let this happen for nothing.
你愈合得很快
You're healing quickly.
再过几天就能继续工作了
Should be ready to jump back into it in a couple more days.
这样应该就行了
Well, that should about do it.
你怎么知道崔维特是医生的？
How'd you know Trevitt was a doctor?
所以你才让我给他打错了药 对吗？
That's why you had me give him the wrong meds, right?
你借我的手杀了他
Why you had me kill him.
因为如果他活下来 就会多一个医生
Because if he had lived, there'd be another doctor
道恩就不需要你了
and Dawn wouldn't need you.
她不会再保护你
She wouldn't protect you.
崔维特是圣依纳爵医院的肿瘤学家
Trevitt was an oncologist at St. Ignatius.
我认识他
I knew him.
他们会赶走我的
They would have kicked me out.
戈尔曼也许会…
Maybe Gorman...
他也许会杀了我
maybe he would have killed me.
我别无选择
I didn't have a choice.
利用一切可以用的资源
Use everything you can use.
当他们抓住耶稣时
When they arrested Christ,
彼得否认自己是门徒之一
Peter denied being one of his disciples.
他别无选择
He didn't have a choice.
否则他们也会把他钉在十字架上
They would have crucified him, too.